# Manchala Anudeep

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

anudeepmanchala4@gmail.com

6361823637

linkedin.com/in/anudeep-m-306671215

https://anudeepmanchala.netlify.app/#hero

# **Summary**

I am currently working as a Data Science Trainee at Turing Minds.Ai . I am Pursing Ai&MI course At INSOFE Institute Bengaluru. I am good at Front End (HTML,CSS,JAVA SCRIPT).I worked As a Web app developer for Mrs. . B's Buzzing home Day care As an intern from August 2021 to October 2021

# **Experience**

## **Web Application Developer**

Mrs. B's Buzzing Home Day Care Aug 2021 - Oct 2021 (3 months)

#### **Data Science Trainee**

TuringMinds.Ai
Feb 2022 - Present (6 months +)

### **Education**



# Sri Chaitanya College of Education

Intermediate 2015 - 2017



#### Narayana Institute

10th 2014 - 2015

# **MVJ College of Engineering**

B.E,CSE 2017 - 2022

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

PGP CDS INSOFE - International School of Engineering (INSOFE)

#### Skills

c • sql • Java • JavaScript • HTML5 • css • python • Tableau • Hadoop